# DENIS MOREIRA DA SILVA

## PERSONAL DETAILS

1341590VA

Nationality: Brazilian Address: Apt23 The Tolka, Prospect Hill. Finglas Rd.

Dublin. Co Dublin. EirCode.: D11 PY99 Email: deniscamilo13@hotmail.com

**Date of Birth:** 03.08.1981 **Mobile:** (089) 9806324

# **OBJECTIVE**

PPS n.:

I want to achieve a career that can gives me countless job opportunities and superior skills helping to grow in my professional career and also in personal life. Changing career has always been one of my goals in life and I feel that now is a great opportunity.

#### **SUMMARY**

Transitioning from of the aviation area in which I worked in the last 4 years and seeking a full-time role in the business field having more than 10 years of experience working in all administrative areas such as customer services, taxes, buying and selling goods, human resources. Initiative, dynamism, organization, problem solving, excellent interpersonal skills, teamwork, perseverance and motivation, ability to work under pressure, able to perform a variety of tasks and quick learner.

I am a very versatile person, I can adapt easily to people and anywhere, I like to work in groups or alone, work in the office or at home. I am searching a career that can help me achieve my goals and provide greater financial stability for my life

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

• Aer Lingus Limited- Address: Dublin Airport

2018-2020

Worked as <u>Baggage Handler</u> doing several tasks as loading, flight responsible to send containers, closing the flights in the baggage hall.

• Swissport Ireland Limited- Address: Cargo Terminal - Dublin Airport

2016-2018

Worked as <u>Aircraft Cleaner</u> in aircraft appearance. Also doing <u>Security Check</u> on the cabin and on the Ground.

• The Lo-cal Kitchen- Address: Unit 4 The Phoenix Park Racecourse, Castleknock, Dublin 15. 2014 - 2016

Worked as a Kitchen Porter at this Irish café and restaurant.

• Store Casa do Nene - Recife-PE, Brazil.

2002-2013

Worked as Executive Supervisor (Partner) at this store in Brazil.

### **EDUCATION**

UFPE- Federal University of Pernambuco (Brazil) - Completed Bachelor of Business

2005

**SEBRAE** (Brazil) Completed a course of <u>Introduction to Entrepreneurship</u> at Brazilian Support Service for Micro and Small Enterprises

2006

#### **CURRENTLY STUDYING**

**Diploma in Software Development –** *Code Institute (Part Time)* 

Google IT Support Professional – Coursera (Part Time)

### **COMPUTER**

Microsoft Office Internet – Advanced

### **HOBBIES AN INTERESTS**

My hobbies are many. I love cycling, since I started living in Dublin I bought a bicycle and it became my first passion to become an active person, I love cycling to the mountains of Dublin or Wicklow and then go hiking. Cinema is also one of my greatest passions in life, I usually tell my friends that cinema is my second home. I am an easy going, friendly, responsible and highly motivated person for the things I want and pursuit. I have always had great responsibilities since I was a teenager managing the family business and when I start something I go through with it.

#### REFERENCE

Stephen Connolly (The Lo-cal Kitchen) - 086 804-5349

Micael O'Hagan (Swissport - Manager Operations) - 087 363-8279

Vincent McGill (Aer Lingus - Surpervisor) - 086 804-5349